

YAN KYAW MIN

FullStack Developer

- +66 0986933771
- @ykm7181
- </> https://github.com/ykmDev
- in www.linkedin.com/in/yan-kyaw-min-ykm
- 🔀 yankyawmin.ykm@gmail.com
- www.yankyawmin.tech
- \$\text{31/05/1995}
- 29 yr
- 🕮 Myanmar/Burma
- 648 Thanon Pracha Uthit 18, Huai Khwang, Bangkok.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology(EC)
Myingyan GTC
2013 - 2016

Bachelor of Engineering(EC)

Myingyan GTC 2016 - 2018

AWARD

1st Winner at Job-matching Hackathon (JICA)

LANGUAGE

English(Fluent)

Thai(Basic)

Myanmar(Native)

ABOUT ME

I'm over 5 years exp in Web development mainly JS and PHP. I've worked in 10+ projects and 2 freelance projects as a Leader in past company.

In Dec 2023 Job-matching Hackathon (JICA) in Myanmar, I'm a mentor of 1st Winner team.

I'm dedicated to leveraging technology to make a positive impact. Let's connect and discuss how we can work together to bring your projects to life!

WORK EXPERIENCE

METATEAM MYANMAR Co., Ltd.

O March 2019 - Oct 2020 Junior Web Developer

- WordPress, Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery
- PHP (Laravel), NuxtJs(Vuejs), Docker, Circle Ci

Oct 2020 - Sept 2022

Senior Web Developer

- Nodejs, Express.js, NuxtJs(Vuejs), PHP (Laravel), Docker, Circle Ci
- Front end and backend coding
- Code review, Operation check and member support.

Sept 2022 - March 2024

Lead Web Developer

- Nodejs (Express.js, Vuejs, NuxtJs),
- PHP (Laravel),
- CMS WordPress, movable Type
- AWS services concerned with web, Docker
- SSH, Github Actions, Circle Ci
- Maintenance(performance, hotfix, deploy and release)
- SSL certificate, LB version/license update

iMyanmarHouse Co.Ltd.

O March 2024 - May 2024 Lead Web Developer

- Project planning, investigating
- Team Building, structure
- DB structure, optimizing
- Code review, Operation review, unit testing
- JS (Vuejs), PHP (Laravel),

SKILL

LANG

- HTML,CSS, SCSS, SASS, Javascript
- JSON, Nodejs, PHP
- Bash script, Python
- Git

DB

- SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MariaDB, Amazon Aurora
- MSSQL
- AWS DynamoDB

CI/CD FLOW

- Manually deploy (by SSH, FTP)
- AWS Code deploy, Laravel Vapor
- Circle Ci, ansible

FRA/LIB

- VueJS, NuxtJS, ReactJS, Typescript
- Laravel, Filament Laravel
- CMS WordPress, Movable Type
- Redis, MongoDB, DynamoDB
- Bootstrap, Tailwind

USE TOOLS

- Figma, Adobe XD
- Draw.io, dbdiagram.io, Postman, Code editors, VsCode, Git-clients, Fork, JIRA

DEV ENV

- AWS services concerned with web development, Digital Ocean
- Render, Vercel
- Docker, Vagrant
- GitHub, Gitlab, Bitbucket

PROJECTS

1) MONASTERY MANAGEMENT PROJECT

site: https://punyarrama.com/yawgi/create/public

Using Tech: Laravel 10, ReactJs, MySQL, Nginx, Digital Ocean Droplet

- Yogi monk easily manage the entry and exit of nuns
- · You can easily add different types of meditation centers
- Various types of room categories are systematically organized.
- Smart cards are issued to yogis so that they don't have to go to register in the future

2) HACKATHON PROJECT

Using Tech: Laravel v10, ReactJs, MySQL, Nginx, AWS EC2, S3

- Can make Preorder by customer
- To approve/denied preorder by Sale department
- To assign preorder to Truck by Logistic department
- To delivery preorder's products by Truck driver
- To Add/edit/Update/Delete stocks and products by Warehouse

3) PROPERTY FOR BUY, SALE & RENT PROJECT

Using Tech: Nodejs, Express.js, Vuejs v3, MySQL, Nginx, Digital Ocean Droplet

- To buy, sell, rent property easily by end-user
- Can search Property easily by location and Map
- Two admin portal for admin and partners
- Language switch by 2 countries (MM and Eng)